

□ (+60) 14-881-7836 | **>** byu1628@protonmail.com | **□** gohanko | **□** gohanko

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary_

Building software for the web — experienced in the Javascript and Python ecosystem.

Skills

Languages Javascript, Python, Perl5

Tooling Git, Bash, Linux, Mobx, Lerna, grunt/gulp, npm/yarn

Frameworks React, Hapi, Django, Django Rest Framework, Flask, Scrapy, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL

Industry Knowledge CI/CD, Agile Software Development

Work Experience _____

Vox Sdn. Bhd.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Kuala Lumpur, Federal Territory of Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Feb. 2021 - March. 2021

- Use Django, Kubernetes, Docker, and PostgreSQL to build and deploy web applications.
- Guided junior developers through technical problems.
- Responsible for development of parts of a REST API that interacts with an AI back-end.
- Responsible for deployment of the back-end REST API using Kubernetes and Docker.
- Participated in daily scrum/agile meetings (technical) and weekly company meetings.
- Collaborated with other developers in building, and maintaining web applications.

Binary Group Services Sdn. Bhd.

Cyberjaya, Selangor, Malaysia

Dec. 2018 - Dec. 2020

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Learned and adopted new technology quickly (Javascript/Perl5).
- Use React, Grunt, Mobx, Webpack and SASS to build and maintain frontend applications.
- Implement a chat application by integrating SendBird's chat API.
- Coordinate with UI/UX to implement designs for our web applications using tools such as Abstract, Zeplin and Invision.
- Collaborated with compliance to make sure our software complies with the laws.
- Use NodeJS, Docker, and PostgreSQL to build server side services for automating payments.
- Participated in typical software development process such as sprint meetings, and code reviews.
- Autonomously outline work and set backlog along with prioritization.
- Help our recruitment team with proctoring new tech candidates in our hackathon.

Freelance Malaysia

• Use Diango, and Diango Rest Framework to build a REST API for an over-the-counter payment tracking service.

• Collaborated with project managers, company owners and other engineers over the internet to work on projects requested.

Education

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

University Tunku Abdul Rahman

Kampar, Perak, Malaysia

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION SYSTEMS (HONOURS) INFORMATION SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

May. 2021 - May. 2024

Jul. 2017 - Jun. 2018

• 3.0 CGPA

Riam Road Secondary School

Miri, Malaysia Jan. 2014 - Dec. 2016

MALAYSIAN CERTIFICATE OF EXAMINATION

• The Malaysian Certificate of Examination is the equivalent of the GCSE in England or GCE Ordinary Level in the Commonwealth of Nations.

- Scored a 3A 4B in the examination which includes Mathematics (A-), Science (A), English (A), Malay (B+), Moral Studies (B+), History (B), and Art (B+).
- The English subject has 2 results, one is the MCE result and the other is the GCE Ordinary Level result, in which I scored an A as well.

November 28, 2021 Brandon Yii · Résumé 1